they
они
will learn if I’m from Ukraine, of course, from
научатся если я с украины конечно от
spring I’m a patriot of my country yes,
весну я патриот своей страны да
we’re like him there and we can’t of course
мы там типа ним и не сможет конечно
we can,
сможем
for example, look,
например смотри
come on, look
давай давай так смотри
how many presidents you had,
сколько у вас было президентов
don’t
не
look, look, look,
смотри смотри смотри
this is
вот
not how I want to show you by example,
не так я тебе хочу показать на примере
we are free people  we want we want to
мы свободные люди мы хотим мы хотим
splashed elected one president we don't
избрызгал избрали одного президента не
want to elect another one we have
хотим избрали другой у вас у нас у нас
people want to pour you against the police
люди хотят влейте вас против полиции
they are afraid dugouts to swell you understand there
боятся блиндажи пухнуть понимаешь там
like for rallies
типа на митинги
but why
но почему
we are free people
мы свободные люди
in that we can do what we want and
в том что мы можем делать что хотим и
how
как
but because  I look because here you
но потому что смотрю потому что вот ты
can go out now, for example, I can go out in
можешь выйти сейчас я например могу в
my city with a poster, for example,
своем городе выйти с плакатом например
there the president is a fool,
там президент дурак
you can’t violate and they’ll immediately
не можешь нарушить а загребут сразу
get a
давал себе
lot of friends to
куча знакомых
repeat yourself, you won’t be able to repeat
повторить не сможешь
[music]
[музыка]
what city are you looking from and a skipping rope
ты с какого города посмотрит и скакалка
from Krasnodar so look you  you say
с краснодара так вот смотри ты говоришь
something like what we have achieved, here I am from the city of
типа чего мы достигли вот я из города
Khmelnitsky
хмельницкий
so we have, for example,
так у нас есть например вот
well-being and yourself, you
благосостоянием и себе вы нормально
live normally with us in the EU  to spend money on a
живем у нас есть деньги на стоматолога
dentist look at my teeth so I
вот посмотри посмотри на мои зубы так я
can provide myself with normal
могу себе обеспечить нормальный уход за
dental care show your teeth here and the
зубами покажи свои зубы вот и рынке
akida market you can’t seem to be a rich cool
акида ты не можешь вроде богатая крутая
country but you can’t go to the dentist yourself
страна но не можешь на стоматолога себе
my teeth
сейчас по зубам мой
from where the apartment is, I’m looking at
от причем квартиру я вот смотри об
recording your teeth
записи зубы твои
up to
своей до
80 apartments and
80 квартир а
why not 300 square
зачем не 300 квадрат
why should I remove it, only I will have to
зачем мне это убирать только надо будет
arrange the cop why
расставлять мент зачем
look here you are an
посмотри вот ты
apartment not an apartment 8 I communicate with you
квартира не квартира 8 я с тобой общаюсь
I see your teeth and a tear and you understand
я вижу твои зубы и слезу и понимаешь
because what a great country you
потому что великая страна ты чего
have achieved we have achieved that in our country the
добились мы мы добились того что у нас
average person can
среднестатистический человек может себе
provide himself with a normal jaw can
обеспечить нормальную челюсть может
go to the dentist to pay money for him
пойти к стоматологу заплатить деньги ему
to do it normally a few not even in the
сделать нормально несколько даже не в
state
государстве
yet
еще
yet how much does this plastic
пока на сколько стоит это пластиковое
window cost how much does this plasma cost [ __ ]
окно на сколько стоит эта плазма нахуй
how much  is the pendant worth the taste
сколько стоит ли подвески на вкус
how much does any friend cost ok [ __ ] him
сколько стоит любой друг ладно хуй с ним
how much does it cost these doors on the way how much
сколько стоит эти двери на путь сколько
don't give a [ __ ], come on, how much does
стоят не бать давай сколько стоит вот
this apartment cost how much does it cost at the kitchen
эта квартира сколько стоит у кухонный
corner [ __ ] how much does it cost here it's
уголок [__] сколько стоит вот это
possible let's see how much
возможно давай посмотрим сколько [__]
it costs [ __ ] [ __ ] come on
стоит нахуй [__] давай
for a global
для глобальных
house with 300 square
дом на 300 квадрат
teeth you can't now show the light bulb does not
зубы не можешь сейчас покажу лампочка не
turn on
включается
our president pendant our people have
наш президент кулон у наших людей
normal teeth
нормальные зубы
my president is the file of your allah and but I
мой президент файла твоих аллаха и но у
have normal teeth you have no teeth
меня нормальные зубы у тебя нет зубов у
you have a light bulb no light bulb not work
тебя лампочки нет лампочки не работу
boots
ботики
you can’t buy a normal paw
ты не можешь нормальный лапу купить
that doesn’t burn out
который не перегорает
show show I don’t believe to go nuts
покажи покажи не верю [__]
American watches are
американские часы
very, very Russian
очень-очень и русский
about something like that, for example, American  bought
о чём вот например то американские купил
this and
this и а
who do you work for
ты кем работаешь
money falls from the sky
деньги с неба падает
but there is that is
но есть то есть
why the
поэтому
teeth of the way it's really funny
зубы пути это это реально смешно
well, because how much how much how much
ну вот потому что сколько сколько стоит
does it cost you they gave you an injection that you were
сколько стоит тебе сделали укол что ты
[ __ ] not afraid of sleeping and those
блин лежал не боялся ничего спал и те
why
почему
you hide yours or not  because you
ты прячешь своих либо не потому что ты
can't forget and I'm a happy person
не можешь забыть и я счастливый человек
I'm sitting there with headphones for 200 rubles
я сижу там с наушниками за 200 рублевкой
so you 200  I can smile I am a
таков тебя 200 я могу улыбаться я
free person I smile you can
свободный человек я улыбаюсь ты можешь
see everything you can take and you hide
видеть все может возьми а ты прячешься
like this even a piece of meat quickly show
вот так даже кусок мяса быстро показать
you
вам